[{"answer": "You know it's actually nothing quiet about the confidence here.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Dana, what is the mood there, is it quite confident or slightly twitchy?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Well, it's kind of up and down mood here, Piers.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Any sign of white flags being raised yet, Peter, or is there a little bit poke in the air?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well, win is a win obviously.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Should they be panicking slightly in the McAuliffe camp and if he just sneaks over the line, what is that say for the bigger picture?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Well, I think the votes that are still out as John was talking about looked very good for Terry.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "The spirit Dana Bash told me of quite noisy confidence down there, was that how you would describe it?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, listen, I think the American politics which has always had a strain and extremism but after we swing outside of that strain it comes back to a more moderate.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "If they take a defeat tonight albeit quite a close one by the look of it, what will that do to Senator Cruz's chances of keeping his momentum going?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Well, I think that (inaudible) prognostic aid (ph), I do know that as a former governor, governor's more than I think senators are sometimes viewed by actually what they get done.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Is he more of a threat perhaps another Romney-type character or you want it Ted Cruz?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Certainly the margin is closer than expected.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Is this surprising to you that is going down to the wire like this?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "With me now, on the left Crossfire's Van Jones, on the right is his co-host, Newt Gingrich.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's remarkable and you have McAuliffe in some polls, 15 points ahead 10 days ago.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Let's start with Virginia, Newt Gingrich, pretty close over there likely still you would say that McAuliffe will edge it but what does it say that it's been so close?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think it's very interesting.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "I mean, if you took that out, could Cuccinelli have possibly won this?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, I think he certainly has a real possibility of convincing people.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Can he convince his own party that he's the man that can actually win a general election?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Wolf and John, thank you both very much indeed.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Well, that's the case.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "So what does it say?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Jake Tapper, fascinating stuff with the man of the moment tonight and let's go right to Wolf Blitzer in Washington.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Look at this and I must say, wow, it's getting really close only 386 votes, Ken Cuccinelli ahead of Terry McAuliffe the Republican had the Democrat by, well it's just changed now it's almost 5,000.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Wolf you've got an update for us from Virginia?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Ken Cuccinelli run better in Virginia than Mitt Romney.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "ORGAN: Bill Kristol, let me turn to you, is it a big defeat for the Tea Party what's happened in Virginia even though it's so close or is the reality that if you haven't had this independent candidate getting perhaps of the 7 percent of the vote, then, they could have won and that it would have been a big win?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "I read it as a rejection of the Republican Party.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Well, how are you reading tonight?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "I think the one thing we know now about 2016 is that Chris Christie is a big player.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Candy, how much significance can be really attached to what is going on tonight?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I think we have something that Terry McAuliffe supporters are going to be happy to hear.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Wolf do we have a verdict?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "That is an understatement.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "I take it they're all pretty excited?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "He did it by winning where the people.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "John how did he do it?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "You know, I just got an e-mail from a Republican running for Federal Office in 2014, you know, the competitive race, and here's what he says.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "What are going to be the key themes going forward?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "Well look, I think that it's no secret that Republicans oppose ObamaCare but candidates matter here, campaigns matter and Terry ran a great race.", "docId": "131105pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Stephanie how will the Obama Administration repel this, given that's fairly where the assault will come?", "qSentId": 569}]